but I know that this is quality, this is the
но я знаю что йл - это качество это
level of more than one generation already, like why did I
уровень не одно поколение уже типа зачем
understand? No, well, wait a second, I
понял Да не ну Подождите секунду я
want to continue now, and you all want to
сейчас хочу продолжить и вы всё хотите
boil it down to the fact that Russia doesn’t
свести к тому что типа Россия ничего не
produce anything. I don’t want it, I’m just not this.
производит Я не хочу я просто не это
Look, you see this here  you got
Смотри видишь это вот у тебя выскочила
this pain I just with I just asked what
эта боль Я просто с Я просто спросил что
you have in your
у тебя в барбершопе
Russian barbershop Hello, you are a blogger Yes I am
российского Здравствуйте Вы блогер Да я
on YouTube now yes yes we can
сейчас на юбе да да отлично можем
communicate great with pleasure
пообщаться с удовольствием
super and what do you usually communicate with Well people
супер а чём общаетесь обычно Ну вот люди
come complaining about their
приходят жалуются на свои
problems how are you as a psychologist Yes
проблемы какси вы как психолог Да
psychotherapist oh psychotherapist class I
психотерапевт о психотерапевт класс я
went to several sessions What happened to you,
ходил на несколько сеансов Что у вас
what worried you and drove you
случилось что вас тревожило да загонял
about studying there, stress because of this I
по поводу учёбы там стресова из-за этого
couldn’t let go, but it happened a long time ago
не мог выпустить но это давно было во
during my studies 4-5 years ago Here are the
время учёбы ещё 4-5 лет назад Вот
delays in relationships with the opposite
а задержки отношениям с противоположным
sex  Were at that time not not everything
полом были в это время не не всё
was fine it was just just
нормально было только вот просто просто
stress and that’s all And it seemed to slightly
стресова и всё И это как бы чуть-чуть
reduce the quality of life or something and that’s all
качество жизни уменьшало что ли и всё
Yeah
Угу
Got it interesting yes yes And what helped Yes I
Понял интересно да да И что помогло Да 9
drank for almost 9 months and not 9 months a little
месяцев пил почти и не 9 месяцев чуть
more and  It helped okay, yes it helped
больше и помогло нормально да помогло
that you drank for 9 months,
что пили 9 меся
yes they drank, I thought they drank, they didn’t drink in
да те а пили я думал пили бухали не в
the sense of these antidepressants that the doctor
смысле эти антидепрессанты которые врач
prescribed. I understand that you were drinking antidepressants for 9 months.
прописал Поня это вы 9 месяцев пили
Yes, I just see that
антидепрессанты Да я просто смотрю что
you say so calmly. I guess they
Вы так спокойно Говорите Походу они до
still work. No, I always do.  no
сих пор действуют Да нет я всегда нет
it was how many years n ago and years n yes Well,
это было сколько лет п назад а лет п да
yes, they didn’t hold it anymore, I agree, yes, what’s
Ну да уже не держали согласен да что ва
bothering you at all, nothing is bothering you,
тревожит вообще ничего трево
everything is Good
всё Хорошая
work, stress, minimum, I sleep well, I eat well,
работа стресса минимум сплю хорошо Ем
everything is great, who are
хорошо всё клас с кем
you sleeping with, with your wife, Oh, okay, Well, that means it’s
спите с женой О нормально Ну значит
good, yes, thank you, But you can  Then the
хорошо да спасибо А вот можно Тогда
question is: Why are you broadcasting like this?
вопрос такой А почему вы ведёте так эфир
Well,
Ну Для
why? The point is that I have my own
чего Дело в том что у меня есть свой
training system, so I conduct
система тренингов так я провожу
psychological practices on YouTube
психологические практики и на YouTube
streams. I'm still telling
стримах Я пока
people how to work with
людям Как можно работать с возражениями
people's objections, how can you work with
людей так как можно работать с
calming, how can you calm down violent people?  that
успокоения так как буйных успокаивать то
is, in different ways, for example, I relieve stress from
есть Разно например стресс снимаю с
people in every way. So I just have
людей по-всякому Так у меня есть просто
students pay me. Well, it’s like I have an
ученики мне платят Ну как бы у меня есть
open one, like, well, a system,
открытый такой как бы ну система вот
usually we have all sorts of psychological
обычно у нас как психологические всякие
trainings like you pay for the entrance there,
тренинги типа ты платишь за вход там
for example, yes, I do a different one  I have a
например да я делаю другая у меня
Premium system Yes, you come for
система Премиум Да вот ты приходишь
free Yes, but you can If you
бесплатно Да но ты можешь Если тебе
like this training, you can
нравится этот тренинг ты можешь там
pay there as much as you want Yes, for example,
заплатить сколько хочешь Да например вот
in the form of a donation Yes, you pay for if you
в виде доната Да ты платишь за если тебе
liked this training Yes, you
понравился вот этот тренинг Да ты
pay as much as you want Yes,
оплачиваешь столько сколько хочешь Да
someone  maybe 10
кто-то может 10
kopecks, maybe 1,000 Green, like, that
гривенник то-то может 1.000 Грин типа то
is, how useful this training will be
есть насколько вот полезный будет этот
Yes And here I am, yes I am using the example of
тренинг Да И вот я да я я на примере
people because chat roulette is very
людей потому что чат рулетки очень
different, there are violent ones, there are psychopaths Yes, I’m
разные есть буйные есть психопаты Да я
figuring out how to communicate with them
вот разбираю как с ними общаться
For example, you can Oh, cool  Let’s say
Например можно О прикольно Допустим мы с
you and I have been communicating for about three minutes now,
вами сейчас уже общаемся сколько минуты
probably, and how are there some sort of
три наверное и как есть какие-то такие
debriefings? Well, I then No, look, I
разборы Ну я потом Нет смотрите я
communicate with the person and then when I
общаюсь с человеком да потом когда
disconnect we debrief with the students Yes,
отключаюсь мы Разбираем с учениками Да
specifically the patient, that is, how, for
вот конкретно пациента да то есть как
example, how the conversation went, what  I
вот например как прошёл разговор какие я
used tricks when talking with him, like
фишки использовал при разговоре с ним да
how I, for example, brought him out so that he could
как я например выводил его чтобы он свою
voice his pain Yes, so that we could show him
боль озвучил Да чтобы мы его показали
so that he would expose his pain Yes, because
чтобы он оголил свою боль Да потому что
what is the problem that many hide their
в чём проблема что многие прячут свою
pain and do not reach it, we must
боль и к ней не достуш мы должны её
draw it out Yes, how  from this school an egg
вытянуть Да как вот из э школу так яйцо
will be born and a chick will be born Yes and then it will
вот цыплёнок родится Да и тогда он будет
be all then we can work it out
ться всё тогда мы можем её проработать
Yes for now this pain is hidden in the middle in the
Да пока эта боль спрятана в середине в
depths Yes psyche we will not
глубинах Да психики мы её никак не
be able to do it in any way so we will beat beat beat the
сможем так вот мы будем бить бить бить
osprey with all
по скопе все вот
these medications  Yes, they don’t work, they
эти медикаменты Да они не действуют они
don’t work. Why Because the reason is
не действуют Почему Потому что причина
always in the middle in the soul. And until
всегда вот в середине в душе Вот и пока
we find this spiritual knot,
мы не найдём вот этот душевный узел не
this clot of energy won’t untie.
развяжет вот это вот сгусток энергии Да
Nothing will happen. The medications don’t work.
ничего не будет медикаменты не действуют
Yes, the medications relieve
Да медикаменты снимают
the symptom,
симптом
you feel better, yes.  you took
есть вам стало легче да вы попили
medications Yes, but the mental problem has not
медикаменты Да но душевная проблема Не
disappeared, medications do not heal the
исчезла медикаменты не лечат
soul No No, look, it seems so to you,
душу Нет Нет смотрите это вам так
that is, medications Yes, they
кажется то есть медикаменты Да они
affected the chemistry in the body Yes, in the
повлияли на химию в организме Да в
body, but not on
организ но не на
Do, well,
Ду ну
once upon a time, for example, we went to the
нужа когда-то ходили например к зубному
dentist, yes, yes they  the painkillers click
врачу да да они обезболивающие щёлкают
so the nervous system is dulled and
так нервная система притупляется и
then they pick your tooth but you don’t feel the pain
дальше вам ковыряют зуб но вы боли не
yes yes that is there is a problem there is a
чувствуете да да то есть проблема есть
hole there for example yes but you don’t
там дырка например да но боли вы не
feel the pain and now you need
чувствуете так и сейчас вам
medications Yes, just to dull
медикаментами Да просто притупить вот
this mental pain yes but the cause has not been
этой душевной боли да но причину не
removed  what is the problem you understand?
убрали вот в чём проблема понимаете Не
No, look how it went for us.
ну смотрите как у нас это проходило Так
So, in addition to medications, there was also
что помимо медикаментов была ещё вот
some kind of work with behavior. Well, this is
работа с поведением какая-то Ну вот это
already Yes, this is already possible, you need to
уже Да это уже возможно тут надо
look here Yes, just medications. I’m
смотреть Да просто медикаменты Я же
saying that medications are like
говорю что медикаменты - Это как Вот
Painkillers and then  yes, but if they
обезболивающие да то есть но если вам
didn’t clean your tooth Yes, they didn’t clean out these
Зуб не почистили Да не прочистили эти
ducts Yes, the medications
канальчик Да всё то медикаменты
will hold out, and then then it starts again
продержатся да потом потом снова начина
and then your head basically falls apart Yes yes,
а потом башка короче развалилась да да
that’s why it’s very important Yes, I’m
поэтому очень важно Да я вот
preaching some kind of medication
проповедуют к медикаментозным каким-то
measures Yes, to relieve this pain Yes, but
мерам Да чтобы снять вот эту боль Да но
first of all, we must find the
в первую очередь мы должны про найти
root cause of the process in the patient Yes,
первопричину процесса в пациенте Да
pull it out, look
вытянуть её разобрать посмотреть с
at it from different angles Yes, look at
разных ракурсов на неё Да просмотреть
how it can be worked out and worked through,
как её можно проработать и проработать
this is already a difficult process yes yes I’ve
это вот уже тяжёлый процесс да да Вот я
also seen people like this who live for years
ещё видел людей таких которые годами
with some kind of chronic  stress with
живут с каким-то хроническим стрессом со
mine there, I don’t know, some kind of tragedy, some kind of
своим там я не знаю трагедия какая-то
study, Not study, and it seems to me that with such people,
учёба Не учёба и вот мне кажется с
probably after all, from the beginning of the
такими уже наверное всё-таки с начало
medication, then this work.
медикамента потом уже вот эта вот работа
Well, look, the medications are not made
Ну смотри не медикаменты делаются
specifically so that a person does not harm himself there,
специально чтобы человек там себе не
because they start there
навредил потому что начинаются там
seizures of some sort, well, yes, but
припадки в какие-то там ну да но всё
still, first of all, we need to work there
равно в первую очередь нужна работа там
with the soul and the psyche, you know, that’s not 100%
с душой с психее понимаете не это 100%
yes yes yes of course, by the way, and
да да да конечно Конечно вот кстати и
now that’s when the
сейчас вот когда началась Вот э
special military operation began. I see
специальная военная операция Я смотрю
that people’s aggravations are here.  these on the
что у людей обострились вот эти на
territory of Russia a
территории России обострились очень
lot of mental processes have intensified because
много психических процессов потому что
you know from TV everywhere there we
знаете с телевизора всюду там мы
will take over there we will take away war war war war
захватим заберём там война война война
war Yes And people used to live there in a
война Да И вот люди раньше жили там в
good information space,
благом информационном пространстве
now they live in an information
сейчас живут в информационном
space of aggression and hatred and
пространстве агрессии и ненависти да и
this is splashing out yes these  internal
это выплёскивает да вот эти внутренние
problems that were sitting in people, they
проблемы которые сидели в людях они
spill out then you saw that
выплёскивается потом вы видели что
the statistics that the amount of
статистику что увеличилось количество
crime has increased, the crime rate has increased
преступности уровень преступности вырос
Yes, violent crimes there are fights,
Да насильственных преступлений там драки
beatings And so on it is growing very much in the
побои И так дальше очень растёт на
Russian Federation This is against the
Российской Федерации Вот это есть на
backdrop of emotional this kind of
фоне эмоционального вот этого такого
negative excitement yes You
негативного возбуждения да Вот Вы
have met among  friends that they also
встречали среди друзей что они тоже
started somehow in a year and a half to
начали как-то за полтора года сво
be more aggressive, no, everything is as it was, it remains so Maybe
быть нет все как были так осталось Может
they are Well, they can
они Ну они могут быть
just be psychopaths, maybe I don’t
просто психопатами может быть такое не
argue with that Yes, it happens that yes, he
спорю Да вот бывает такое что да он
stands then in the eyes He doesn’t care  - he didn’t
стоит потом в оче Ему что-то не
like it, he attacked the cashier and
понравилось он накинулся на кассиршу и
knocked her down, for example, well, not like that Yes, but
сбил там например ну не такое Да но
again this can happen outside the
опять же это может произойти и вне
situation and after the situation during
ситуации и после ситуации во время бы
all these bunks So well, let’s all call
все вот эти вот нар Так ну все назовём
them like this, they’re like before this  and
их вот так вот они как бы бы до этого и
they will be after that, yes But the level, for example,
будут после это да Но уровень например
is when, for example, the EU level of
вот когда например ЕС уровень
cholera, for example, there was
заболевания холерой например там был
one there in 100,000 one in 1, this is already
один там на 100.000 один на 1 это уже
like an epidemic Yes, and here it means that
типа эпидемия Да также и тут это значит
there is a problem, it has been updated somewhere
есть проблема она где-то актуализирована
and it is necessary to monitor it somehow locally  Zro and
и надо её как-то мониторить локали Зро и
extinguish Well, yes, I understood And you get it 5 years
гасить Ну да понял А вы получается 5 лет
ago Yes, you only went to a psychologist, a
назад Да ходили только к психологу
psychotherapist, a psychotherapist, and a
психотерапевту психотерапевту да
psychotherapist, a psychotherapist Well,
психотерапевту психотерапевту Ну да
somewhere, I understood, yes, and this was even before the wedding,
где-то так понял да а это ещё до свадьбы
yes, I understood Well, then you got married, the
у вас было да да понял Ну потом женились
relationship became more harmonious
уже более гармонические отношения стали
Yes  yes yes, when I was studying there, moving away
Да да да когда учился как-то там переезд
from my parents, well, from my parents’ house, all these
от роди Ну из Родительского дома все вот
things are somehow like this. Against this background,
такие вот вещи как-то Вот на этом фоне
everything accumulated and I decided that it would be better for me to go
всё накопилось и я решил что лучше я
instead of saving it all for myself, and it
схожу чем себе копить это всё буду и
helped okay and it turns out, well, now
помогло нормально и получается ну сейчас
that  you have a wife, you are more often in the
когда вот у вас есть жена вы чаще в
biofield of feminine energy,
биополе женской энергетики находитесь
you are no longer, no, well, I still have a
вам уже вы не не не ну как у меня же ещё
job, well, come on, it’s clear, well, yeah, well, you
работа Ну как ну же Ясно Ну да нуно вы
come home, hug your wife, you’re
приходите домой обнимайте жену
not talking to you when you benefit
разговариваете не вас когда вы вас благо
from you, you feel like a man  your
с вы ощущаете себя мужчино у вас
internal tone is rising Well, and
поднимается внутренний там тонус Ну и
externally, of course I understand, it’s cool,
внешний коне конечно Понял да прикольно
thank you, you have a cool approach too I
спасибо У вас тоже классный подход Мне
like it, well, I’m a professional, look,
нравится да Ну я Я профессионал смотрите
I’ve just been working on the Internet for several years now
Я просто же не первый год уже работал
I’ve
просто в интернете Я в чатрулетке
been doing chatroulette for a year and a half Yes, it just
полтора года занимаюсь Да просто раньше
wasn’t enough before  There are now a huge number of patients on chatroulette,
мало было пациентов в чатрулетке сейчас
and I was able to, we used to just go out
количество и я смог мы раньше выходили
on the streets. Yes, and for example, we sorted out
просто на улиц Да и разбирали например
passers-by like that, situationally, but now with
прохожих вот так ситуативно да сейчас с
technology with the Internet, chat roulette
технологиями с интернетом чат рулетка
is just a treasure for modern
это просто клади для современной
psychiatry, like, well, just, you
психиатрии типа ну просто да вы же
understand, yes  You come across some people, yes,
понимаете да какие-то люди попадаются да
yes, you always do. By the way, how do you
да постоянно бывает вы Кстати как
feel about the war against
относитесь к войне против
Ukraine? Honestly, I just went into the chat
Украины честно я сейчас зашёл в чат
just to relax after work somehow. There’s
просто расслабиться после работы как-то
no desire to discuss such topics at all, just like that. Well, look, you
вообще нет просто вот так Ну смотрите
see somewhere, you know  That’s what I
вот видите где-то знаете вот в чём я
understand, you have this block somewhere, you
понял у вас где-то этот блок стоит вы не
can’t express it, that’s usually it. Well, there are no
можете высказать вот обычно Ну сри нет
blocks, there are no
блоков никаких нет
blocks, just, just look. I have a
блоко просто ну просто смотрите Я у меня
degree in political science. Yes, and I know that
образование политолога Да и я знаю что
now only we will talk about this topic.  there
сейчас только мы зайдём на эту тему
will be a conflict with you right away
разговаривать У нас сразу будет с вами
I don’t want to Why not I’m not a
конфликт Я не хочу с Почему не я не
political scientist not these political ones I’m just
политолог не эти политические Я просто
watching So I’m looking at how people react
смотрю Вот я смотрю как люди реагируют
to this question I don’t care how they
на этот вопрос мне всё равно как они
answer I’m interested in the reaction as a
ответят мне интересна реакция как
psychologist I
психологу Я же
don’t understand these authorities Who’s fighting there  here
не понима эти власти Кто там с воюет вот
I am a psychologist Yes, I look, I’m just asking
я психолог Да я смот Я просто задаю
a question, I don’t know what the correct answer
вопрос я не знаю какой правильный ответ
to this question is, but I’m looking at how a person
на этот вопрос но я смотрю Как человек
reacts, you have a block, I can
реагирует вот у вас блок я могу
diagnose a block, you
диагностировать блок вы не
can’t, it’s not a block, I’m just saying that I
может это не бло я просто говорю что я
don’t want to talk about this topic in general  you work as
не хочу на эту тему обща работаете
a political scientist, it turns out No, I work as a
политологом получается Нет я работаю
barber M ba people
барбером М ба людей
gu nano work
гу нано работа
for a long time, as if I decided to try myself in
долго как бы решил попробовать себя в
this field, everything turned out well Well, like, well, before we
этой сфере получилось всё хорошо Ну типа
studied that we didn’t go to become a
ну а до учились что не пошли на
political scientist Well, it’s like, well, I’m
политолога Ну это ж вроде ну вот я же
telling you, while I was studying I became a barber
говорю я пока учился стал барбером
work and I liked it more than
работать и мне понравилось больше чем
all this dirt, this is where I’m sitting,
вот эта вот вся грязь вот это вот я сижу
I’m having a blast, I communicate with people all the time, they
я кайфую я общаюсь с людьми постоянно
always leave me a lot of tips and
мне постоянно много чаевых оставляют и
like, why do I need flattery? I understand, well, let’s
типа зачем мне лесть понял ну Давайте
try to watch. I’m not going to
попробуем смотреть я Я не собираюсь там
argue there, I just want to  I’m not
спорить что-то я хочу просто не я же
saying, I don’t want to communicate on this topic,
говорю я не хочу общаться на эту тему
your position is interesting to me. As a
вашу позицию мне мне интересно Мне как
psychologist, no no, I don’t want it. I want to
психологу Нет нет я не хочу её Я хочу
see how your facial expressions will be during
смотреть как будет как мимика ваша во
the time. Let’s say this right away.
врем давайте так я сразу говорю
Last time I don’t want to communicate on this
Последний раз я не хочу общаться на эту
topic honestly  And you are the last to communicate with you
тему честно А вы ти послед с вами
from the point of view, you start to
пообщаться с точки зрения вы начинаете
get nervous, you see, you start to have
нервничать видите вы начинаете агрессия
some kind of aggression, you set conditions for me, I’m
какая-то вы мне условия ставьте я
telling you for the last time Well, it was
последний раз говорю Ну это была
aggression, it was a manifestation of aggression
агрессия это было проявление агрессии
No, it was you were tough, you made a
Нет это было вы жёстко вы сделали
tough gesture, a gesture and an ultimatum, I’m the
жёсткий жест жест и Ультиматум я
last  since you said so it was it was
последний раз вы так сказали это было
aggression put pressure on me you
это агрессия была давите на меня вы
put pressure on me
давите ме
No I told you please let’s not
Нет я вам сказал пожалуйста давайте не
put pressure I have the right to speak you have the
давлю я имею право говорить вы имеете
right to answer and not answer yes yes I
право отвечать и не отвечать да да я
can No I shouldn’t where did my
могу Нет я не должен откуда у меня
debt come from something  accept we don’t have
взялся долг что-то принимать у нас нету
any kind of debt You see, there
какого-то долга Понимаете вот это в
is a debt in your head that I have to
вашей голове есть долг что я должен
accept but you are not aggressive Well, how But how
принять но вы агресси не Ну а как А как
then
тогда
Wait a second I want to I don’t want to
Подождите ну секунду я хочу я не хочу
answer this question And how do you
отвечать на этот вопрос А Вы всё как
react how do you relate how  you relate to
относишься как относишься как относишься
And you wouldn’t be turned on by it in any way No,
А вы вас бы это не завело никак Нет ну
come on Try it, ask me
давайте Попробуйте вот спрашивайте меня
what I’m saying No no no and look
что я говорить Нет нет нет и посмотрите
Yes, I’m a broken record
Да всё у меня заезженная пластинка
I just don’t want to answer this question
Просто я не хочу отвечать на этот вопрос
all Why what happened Well, here I am,
всё Почему что случилось Ну вот я я
look, I’m a professional psychotherapist
смотри я профессиональный психотерапевт
I’ve been through this more than once when
я проходил это не один раз когда
you say to a person Well, tell him No, I won’t
человеку говоришь Ну скажи он Нет не
say Say I won’t tell him and he doesn’t want to, he’s
скажу Скажи Не скажу и он не хочет он
putting pressure on himself, he’s closing himself That’s what I
давит он себе закрывает Вот это в я вам
told you directly, I don’t want to answer that,
прямо сказал я не хочу отвечать на это
so they all say Yes, everyone says that I
вот они все говорят Да все говорят что я
don’t  I want Why Because there is some kind of
не хочу Почему Потому что есть какой-то
internal block that needs to be
внутренний блок который нужно
worked out, your Psyche is internal no
проработать ваша Психея внутренняя не
no I’m
нет Я же вам
just sorry, I’m sorry, I’ll kill you I
прямо извините извините я Вас прибью Я
told you straight I don’t want to
же вам прямо сказал я не хочу с вами
discuss the topic of obsmo with you. Something happened to you
обсуждать тему обс смо Вы у вас что-то
during  training This is
случилось во время обучения Вот это
some kind of mental thing you, because of political science,
какой-то психически вы из-за политологии
you saw, maybe this is this, well,
это вы видели может что это вот это ну
negative Yes, and because of this, you left this
негатив Да и из-за этого вы ушли из этой
sphere, like went to a barber Yes, and in
сферы типа пошли в барбера Да и в
principle, this mental breakdown of yours
принципе вот этот ваш душевный надлом
was also most likely  because of this
тоже скорее всего был из-за вот этой
political
политической
dirt Yes, so I found this reason. You
грязи Да так вот Я нашёл эту причину
see, you need to let go of this
Понимаете вот вот вам надо отпустить это
ease, so talk, talk about
лёгкость вот проговорите проговорите о
politics and that’s it, you’ll finally let go, you
политике и всё и Вам станет вы отпустите
see you’re holding these
окончательно видите вы держите вот эти
medications again, you’ll have to use them again, you know,
медикаменты снова придётся понимаете
then it’ll come out now these
употреблять Потом оно вылезет сейчас эти
Simonyan skobeeva Simonyan beevo like a nightingale
симоньян скобеева Симонян беево соловью
it will start it will come out you see you need to
оно начнёт оно вылезет видите нужно
let go of yourself from the middle and
отпустить из себя из середины и
say what we are not afraid of we
проговорить то что мы не боимся мы
say what we are Well, if this thing
говорим то что нас Ну вот если эта вещь
you are afraid to voice it, it means it
вы боитесь её озвучить Значит она вас
controls you and not you, you understand
контролирует а не вы её вы понимаете
what you need
что вам надо мотиватором
to be a motivator is not You control, yes, you do not
быть не Вы контролируете да не вы
control this problem, but the problem
контролируете эту проблему а проблема
controls you, no, you cannot
контролирует вас нет вы не можете её
voice it, it tells you, I don’t voice it, I do
озвучить она тебе говорит не озвучиваю
n’t voice it, I don’t want to, I don’t have to,
меня не озвучиваю я не хочу не надо
you see it’s an inner voice That’s what it
видишь это внутренний голос Так тебе
says to you, it turns out yes Absolutely true,
говорит получается да Абсолютно верно
absolutely yes, yes Well, you  you are afraid of everything And you
абсолютно так да Ну ты боишься всё И ты
justify, you see, you justify that
оправдываешь видишь ты оправдываешь что
no, this is not true. An excuse is
нет нет это не правда Вот оправдание -
one of the first signs that it
это одно из первых признаков того что
exists. Yes, if, for example, they say something about me.
есть это да если например на меня скажут
On the street, for example, you weigh 100
Вот на улице ты например там весишь 100
kg, I won’t make excuses that I weigh
кг я же не буду оправдываться что я вешу
100  kg because I know that I don’t weigh
100 кг потому что я знаю что я вешу не
100 kg Yes, I’ll go further I won’t And
100 кг Да я пойду дальше я не буду А
if a person is plump Yes he will say and
если на человека полненькой Да скажет а
he weighs 110 Yes for example he will say you
он весит там 110 Да например скажет ты
weigh 100 kg he no no no I’m not 100 I’m
весишь 100 кг он нет нет нет я не 100 я
98 Oprah will already start  Your sanology
98 уже начнёт опра вот у вас санология
is great, but it doesn’t work, it
классная но оной она не работает
works, well, look, you’re
работает работает ну смотрите Вы
absolutely the same as the others,
абсолютно такой же самый как остальные
everyone is the
все па
same, this is not a sick patient, this is not a sick
оди паци это не больной не больной
patient - this is a person who
пациент - это человек который
interacts with a doctor, including a
взаимодействует с доктором в том числе с
psychotherapist. Yes, I’m telling you, I’ve already
психотерапевтом Да говорю я уже сво
left.  you and I, aubrey, I can’t just
отходил мы с вами обри Нельзя просто мне
honestly, it hurts for a second, now
если честно боль секунду я ва сейчас
I’m more interested in other things,
пере мне больше интересно другие вещи
some kind of politics, somehow
какие-то политику как-то
obs from zan
обс из занов
politics, don’t discuss intimacy, and these
политику не обсуждать интим и вот эти
are the things that are always
вот вещи они всегда
taboo, and we’ll see now, you’re
табуированные и мы сейчас посмотрим Вы
hanging on again  I'm labeled Afraid
опять навешивается на меня ярлык Боитесь
I'm not afraid I just don't want to I
Я же я не боюсь я просто не хочу У меня
have people with whom I communicate on a
есть люди с которыми я общаюсь на
political topic
политическую тему
Name the topic that you just
Назовите тему на которую вы просто
want to talk about why so immediately
хотите поговорить почему такая сразу
condescending I changed I changed from a
снисходительно я сменил я сменил с
negative topic yes to a
негативной темы да на коннотацию на
positive connotation I say well  ok, it was
позитивную я гово ну ладно прикольно
cool, it was cool I liked it, I must
прикольно был Мне понравилось надо
remember It was cool, I liked it,
запомнить Прикольно мне понравилось буду
I will also use movies, books, I don’t
использовать также фильмы книги Я не
know sports, these are the things sports
знаю спорт вот такие вот вещи спорт
sports I like sports, okay,
спорт Мне нравится спорт хорошо да
look, why do you think that now
смотрите Как вы считаете почему сейчас
Russian athletes are banned from
российских спортсменов Запрещают им
performing under the Russian flag at
выступление под российским флагом на
many I understand you  competitions,
многих Я вас понял соревнованиях
you also have problems with sports Yes, with
у вас со спортом тоже проблемы Да с
this Yes, why with this
таким Да ну почему с таким
Yes, I’m waiting for an answer Well, I won’t discuss
Да я жду ответа Ну я не буду обсуждать
this topic. I’m telling you already, sports is
эту тему Я же вам говорю уже спорт у вас
everything for you. Why in sports Why are you
всё Почему в спорте Почему вы мне
asking me, a Ukrainian, questions about Russia at all,
украинцу задаёте вообще вопросы про
I don’t understand  Are you even from
Россию я не понимаю вы вообще откуда из
Kiev? Which one are you from Kiev? Don’t tell
Киева Какой ты из Киева не рассказывай
me Krylov’s fables Why don’t you believe me? I don’t believe you. Why don’t I believe you?
басни Крылова Почем смы вы мне не верите
Why do we have Ukraine in Kiev, barbers don’t
Почему у нас Украина в Киеве барберы не
cut their hair as badly
так стригутся
as bad?
как плохо
this is
психов Ты что значит оскорбили это
manipulation see you Manipura was accused of
манипуляция видишь ты манипуру обвиняли
manipulation no look I asked a very
манипуляци нет смотри я задал очень
simple question yes to sports Look you
простой вопрос да спорту Смотри ты
asked said you asked some
спросил сказал ты зада какие-то вопросы
incomprehensible questions that I am like a patient client I am
непонятные что я типа пациент клиент я
telling you that no we communicate
тебе говорю что нет мы общаемся равно
just like you are a citizen of your country I am a
просто как ты гражданин своей страны Я
citizen of my
гражданин своей
country  when you ask questions politically
страны когда задаёшь вопросы политически
whatever you want I asked about sports I don’t like
что хочешь Я по спорту задал не нравится
sports give me another topic Choose So you’ll
спорт давай другую тему Выбери Так ты
bring it up again Paulie I don’t know Well Choose
опять сведёшь это Поли не знаю Ну Выбери
a topic Why does politics seem to you everywhere like
тему Почему ту тебе всюду политика
that’s a pain bad for you No
кажется вот э боль вредине тебя Не ну
damn cool you’re
блин классно ты
upsetting it’s great I really liked it
осаживание кайфово Мне очень понравилось
Well  Choose another topic If not sports,
Ну Выбери другую тему Если не спорт
give books books
давай книги книги
yes How to connect this with yours Yes, what do you
да Как это связать со своего Да как ты
think after the last year and a half,
считаешь после вот последние полтора
yes, there is a problem in Russia with
года да ощущается в России проблема с
printed publications with Dude, you're handsome You're
печатными изданиями с Чувак ты красав Ты
just handsome in general, well, how classy
просто красавчик вообще ну как кла класс
Class I like it Well, I don’t know  I just
Класс Мне нравится Ну не знаю я как
bought books and still buy them. Yes, the price
покупал книги так и покупаю Да вот цена
of books
на книг
has increased. Well, maybe. Yes, by the way, there is
выросла Ну может быть Да кстати есть
such a thing; perhaps, that’s what the
такое возможно воз вот в чём
economic effect is: Over the
экономический эффект в том что За
past year and a half, the price
последние полтора года существенна цена
of books in the Russian Federation has increased significantly.
на книги в Российской Федерации выросла
Damn, I wish I had your skill.  how he
ка Блин вот мне бы твой навык ты как его
trained him, it’s really cool. Well, come to
на тренировал прям кайфово Ну приходи ко
my training somehow, yes, at school,
мне на тренинг как-то типа да в школе
at the university, when I was studying, when we
вот в универе когда Я учился когда мы
practiced these debates, we
отрабатывали вот эти вот дебаты
simulated That’s cool, in general,
моделировали Вот классно вообще вот
such a skill would be very useful, it’s cool,
очень пригодилось бы такой навык кайфово
handsome, that’s what you think
класс красавчик то вот как ты думаешь
Why have the prices of books in the Russian Federation gone up in the
Почему подорожали книги в Российской
last year and a half, and I don’t
Федерации последние полтора года а я не
know, I don’t
знаю я в политике не
understand politics, it’s book
разбираюсь во полити это же книго
printing, I don’t understand economics either,
печатания Я в экономии тоже не
not economics, I’ll
разбираюсь не в экономике я вот по
tell you everything by hair, everything
волосам всё тебе расскажу по воло всё
about Barber Svo, let’s talk about Barber Svo  Yes,
про барбер сво давай про барбер сво Да
how do you think about the last
как ты вот как ты считаешь последние
year and a half of the tools
полтора года инструменты в барбершопе
that the barbershop buys, they have become more expensive,
которые закупает они подорожали
also with books it could have been done
также с книгами было може как-то
differently No, well, we’ll start from the beginning with
по-другому Не ну мы начнём сначала с
this, they haven’t become more expensive, they haven’t become more expensive Yes, we have
этого не не подорожали не подорожали Да
our own Russian ones. I understand, that is, you
ус свои российские А понял то есть вы
use  in the barbershop there are Russian
используете в барбершопе российские
tools Yes, almost Who is your
инструменты Да почти Кто у вас
manufacturer of Russian tools
производитель российских инструментов
I wonder who the fishing equipment is no longer
Интересно кто ловя техника это уже не
Russian Russian as the company
Российская российская как фирма
is called Russian Well damn, we have it,
называтся Российская Ну блин У нас есть
but it’s not Russian Well, it’s
да не Российская Ну так это
international No, what’s the
международная Нет ещё раз как
name again, it’s spelled like ra and
называется пишется как ра и
bel barber, you can do that
бел барбер можно так
write How to spell it
написать Как пишется ещ
again and
раз и
English ra yes of course of
английский ра да конечно
course there is no rail
конечно райл
manufacturer
производитель
because the Russian one I’m already telling
нету потому что Российская говорю уже у
you, you just don’t have it because Rossi doesn’t
вас просто её нет потому что Росси не не
no Well no I don’t even see a Russian rebl type
Ну нету Даже российского есть ребл типа
like
как
rebel rail I’m telling you
повстанец райл не вижу я же тебе говорю
because it’s
потому что это
Russian no  show show yes
Российская нету покажи покажи да
some kind of seis
какой-то сейс
paradise no rush no distracting ku no no no
рай не торопишься не отвлекаю ку не не
hurry
спешу
mixed up without and it turns out I always
перепутал без и оказывается я всё время
thought that there was there and there’s just a lll
считал что там есть и а там просто л л л
rebel Yes
повстанец Да
Dada it’s me, we’re just somehow
Дада это я просто у нас как-то в это
having a conversation like this  lll I was always
идёт разговор типа ллл я всегда был
sure that it was there and I understood it’s
уверен что там есть и понял
cool two letters e yes re
прикольно две буквы е да ре
rebel Yes
повстанец Да
no
нет
Russian if I’m not mistaken the word e
Российская если я не ошибаюсь слово ре
yes Scottish it’s okay Scottish
да шотландская это ладно шотландская
Scottish Well, I’m saying this is not a
шотландская Ну так я же говорю это не
Russian product
российское произво
Russian Well rebl yes Scotland I’m just
Российска Ну ребл да Шотландия Я просто
Scotland Scotland  Scotland Well, what are you talking about? What do you
Шотландия Шотландия Шотландия Ну так ты
have in your
что А что у вас российское в
barbershop:
барбершопе
glass and
стекло да
Russian glass and beards and
стекло российское стекло и бород да
glass and beards and Russian people, the most
стекло и бород и люди российские самое
important thing is that the people are Russian and this is
главное что люди российские при это
the most
самое
important thing Scotland is not Scotland England,
главное Шотландия не Шотландия Англия
it doesn’t matter, that is, look, I
это без разницы то есть смотри я
understand correctly that everything
правильно понимаю что все
imported tools yes yes, that is,
инструменты импортные да да то есть
because of sanctions,
из-за санкций
access to these tools is somehow
так доступ к этим инструментам как-то
limited at all there is no
ограничен вообще нет никакого
restriction at all
ограничения нет вообще
Well, yes, steel is a little more expensive there by 10%, maybe it
Ну да чуть дороже стали там на 10% может
has gone up in price and
подорожали и
everything is cool yes Well, a barber can
всё прикольно да Ну барбер может себе
afford such financial ones Well no
позволить такие вот финансовые Ну не
difficulties Well, why? For example,
трудности А хорошо А почему Например
why aren’t there
почему нету российских инструментов
any Russian barber tools? Well, because they don’t
таких барберские Ну потому что не
produce them, or maybe some
производят либо может какие-то
unpopular ones, because if they exist,
непопулярные потому что если есть йл
why should I
зачем мне
use these tools of
использовать вот эти вот инструменты
some dude who doesn’t
какого-то чувака который не
have some kind of cool story? They are
же есть история какая-то классная Они же
Not only have they come out now, they have a
не только сейчас вышли у них есть
cool story, some kind of
классная история какие-то масштабы
global scale. Why should I waste my time
всемирные Зачем мне тратить своё время
trying Russian ones? Are there any
чтобы попробовать российское Есть ли
cool ones? I’m sure there are, but I know that
крутые я уверен что есть но я знаю что
this is quality, this is the level of more than one
йл - это качество это уровень не одно
generation already, like why did I understand? No,
поколение уже типа зачем понял Да не ну
wait  for a second now I want to
Подождите секунду я сейчас хочу
continue and you all want to reduce it to the fact
продолжить и вы всё хотите свести к тому
that Russia doesn’t produce anything.
что типа Россия ничего не производит Я
I don’t want it. I’m just not this. Look, you see
не хочу я просто не это Смотри видишь
this, this pain popped up in you. I’m
это вот у тебя выскочила эта боль Я
just with. I just asked what you have in your
просто с Я просто спросил что у тебя в
Russian barbershop. I didn’t say what.
барбершопе российского Я не сказал что
Russia doesn’t produce anything I just
Россия ничего не производит Я просто
ask what Russian did you say glass
спроси что российского ты сказал стёкла
and people Well yes and
и люди Ну да и
Beard Well
Борода Ну О'кей
Okay okay Well I say the point is for me then
ладно Ну я говорю смысл мне тогда
to buy a dude I don’t know when
покупать чувака которого я не знаю когда
there is a quality product, why is there a
есть качественный продукт зачем то есть
poor quality product in Russia
в России не качественный
associated with a barber  Yes, well, I don’t
продукт связанная с барбером Да ну я не
know. Maybe somewhere there is a quality product
знаю Может где-то есть качественно про
that I don’t know about, but it’s high quality
которое я не знаю но йл качественная во
all over the world, it would be
всём мире бы
clear. I can’t understand if Russia is
понятно я не могу понять если Россия там
launching some kind of missiles, tanks. Are you saying
запускает какие-то там ракеты танки Ты
that it can’t make the tools for a
что она не может инструменты для
hairdressing salon normal? Well, it
парикмахерской сделать нормальной Ну
turns out  can’t And why, how is
получается не может А почему как
this for me, what questions are not just
это ко мне какие вопросы не просто
interesting to me, look at me, I’m just not a
интересно меня смотри я просто я не
political scientist, I’m not an economist. Well, as I
политолог я не экономист Ну вот я как я
understand it, if my country made
понимаю вот если моя страна делала
missiles there Tanks and then what’s not Mola
ракеты там Танки да то что на не Мола
to make
сделать
scissors because
ножницы потому
missiles are tanks here  the state does it
что ракеты танки вот делает государство
from government orders And this is done by people themselves, not a
с госзаказов А это делают люди сами не
state company, again, if
государственная компания опять же если
we take analogies with it, it’s not a
брать аналоги с она же не
state company, there was just
государственная компания просто был
some cool dude who created a company and that’s it.
какой-то крутой чувак создал компанию и
Apparently there are no such people. Why
всё Видимо нет таких людей А почему в
aren’t there cool dudes in Russia that I
России нет крутых чуваков которые мо я
know very well  How do I know? You live in
отку знаю ято откуда знаю Вы живёте в
Russia I’m interested Well, I can say
России Мне интересно Ну я могу сказать
the question in the opposite direction, you do
вопрос в обратную сторону вас же этого
n’t have that either
тоже нет
Three containers, but no in Ukraine we are
Три тара дено во нет в Украине мы
such a small post-Soviet page
маленькая такая постсоветская страничка
Yes, well, not small, the first in Europe if you
Да ну не маленькая первая в Европе если
don’t take Russia, well, we’re not in economics  And
не брать Россию не ну мы по экономике А
in Russia, well, like Russia there, in short, it
в России ну типа Россия там короче у неё
has the opportunity to attack other
есть возможность нападать на другие
countries, but there is no opportunity to make
страны но нет возможности сделать
scissors for barbershops. So I’m
ножницы для барбершопов Так я же ещё раз
saying again everything that you said, it’s done by the
говорю всё что вы сказали это делает
state, and scissors for barbershops are
государство а ножницы для барбершопа
made by people well, but this is
делает человек хорошо а вот это
perfume there for barbershops  Where are you buying from?
парфюмерию там для барбершопа Вы откуда
Honestly, I don’t even know. Well, these world championships are also not
Честно я даже не знаю Ну тоже не
made in Russia. You have a
Российского производства у вас
problem. We have a part
эти ЧМ проблема ро У нас есть часть
that we produce ourselves. And there is a part
которую мы сами производим А есть часть
that we buy in the sense of producing it
которую мы закупаем в смысле производите
ourselves. Well, we produce it ourselves. We have a
сами Ну сами производим У нас есть
separate workshop where we produce fme. But this
отдельный цех где производит фме Но это
produce or just
производите или просто разливает вам
bottle barrels come to you And you bottle
приходят бочки А вы разлива
it, it’s not a production, well, we don’t
по это не производст ну как не
produce Why don’t we produce, we
производим Почему не производим
essentially do something ourselves,
производим по сути что-то сами делаем
look, if I yes, I brought a barrel of kvass Yes,
смотри если я да при привёз бочку кваса
and I bottle it in a glass, I’m not a
Да и и разливаю его в стаканчике я не
kvass producer Yes, I  I agree with this,
производитель кваса Да я согласен с этим
I don’t argue with this Yes, I don’t argue with this, I
с этим не спорю Да я с этим не спорю так
understand that’s what else, ask
и есть понял вот что ещё вот Задай ты
some question that worries you
какой-то вопрос который тебя тревожит
because nothing really
потому что да меня ничего по сути не
bothers me No, this doesn’t happen to everyone,
тревожит Нет не бывает такого у каждого
if if a person says
вот если если человек говорит меня
nothing worries me, it means he understands, he is
ничего не тревожит значит он понимает
aware of his problem but doesn’t want to
осознаёт свою проблему но не хочет
say You can distance yourself from your
сказать Можешь отстраниться от своей
problem say something anything
проблемы скажи что-нибудь что-нибудь
Ask me
Спроси меня
what was the last book you read on
какую вы книгу последнюю читали по
psychology on psychology diagnosis of
психологии по психологии диагностика
mental disorders during military
психических расстройств во время военных
conflicts
конфликтов
class author psychologist Anro Podolsky was
класс автор психолог анро Подольский был
class I’m now reading a book on the social
класс Я сейчас читаю книгу социальная
psychology of Mars, it’s cool and here’s what
психология Марса прикольно и вот Какие
theses you took away from it, I’ve now
тезисы ты вынес из неё я прочитал сейчас
only read about 200 pages about it,
только 200 страниц около она
according to the thesis the fact that I
по тези попу то что
even wrote everything down on my phone
даже в телефон всё на записывал Ну
Well, if you’re interested, don’t you tell
могуть если интересно ну не вы скажите
me I’m interested in what you remember  of these
мне интересно что вы запомнили из этих
200, this is what you liked. I
200 вот что вам понравилось Я вот
read today about how this perception of the
сегодня читал про как это восприятие
past or interpretation of the past is
прошлого или интерпретация прошлого то
that we
что мы
now interpret it from the point of view of those
его сейчас тракту с точки зрения тех
feelings of knowledge of emotions that exist now
чувств знаний эмоций которые есть сейчас
and not from the point of view that was
а не с той точки зрения которая была
then and because of this there may be some
тогда и изза этого могут быть какие-то
-distortions Here And there is one of the theses that
искажения Вот И там один из тезисов что
at different moments in life you can
в разные моменты жизни ты можешь
perceive the past differently. Yes, that
по-разному воспринимать прошлое Да вот
is, you now perceive
то есть вы сейчас да воспринимаете
the past differently than you perceived it a year
прошлое не так как воспринимали его год
ago, and in 10 years you will look at your
назад а через 10 лет будете на своё
childhood even differently
детство смотреть ещё по-другому потому
because based on your new life
что исходя из нового своего жизненного
experience, you will look through the prism of
опыта вы будете смотреть через призму
experience, everything else you liked from
опыта всё что вам ещё понравилось из
this
этой
[music]
[музыка]
book, somehow it all flew out of your head.
книги блин как-то всё из головы по
Well, if you take this
вылетало Ну вот это вот если брать
today, this was the last one Yes, I was
сегодня вот это вот последнее было Да
just driving  Nara was on his way to
ехал как раз Нара послед ехал как раз на
work, I read it, I read it on the way to work
работу читал читаю её по пути на работу
and on the way back from work. That is, you
и по пути с рабо то То есть вы помните
only remember what you read today, and the first thing
только то что читали сегодня да первое
that comes Now, yes, but you can
что приходит Сейчас да А вот можете
remember. Look, if we
вспом Вот смотри если мы вспоминаем
only remember what we read today, this  it means
только то что читали сегодня это значит
we didn’t remember it, but if there
у нас оно не запомнилось вот если что-то
was something significant, we would remember it,
было существенное мы бы его запомнили
that’s what you’ve already read from this book, 200 pages, that’s what you
вот что вы из этой книги 200 страниц вы
remembered somehow strange, since such garbage,
запомнили как-то странно раз такая фигня
you can, as a psychotherapist, tell me
Вы можете как психотерапевт подсказать
what it is, yes What is it  This
что это такое да Что это Это
is called, well, as if the first signs of
называется ну как бы первые признаки
clinical
клинического рассеяния
distraction, yes, perhaps I agree, there is, I
внимания да возможно согласен такое есть
don’t argue with you. It happens, it happens, that you, for example, go, You go, tell someone something and forgot, and Remind me, this is what we talked about, there is this,
мне вот о чём мы говорили есть такое не
no, this  now now is actually the first time
не вот сейчас сейчас вообще первый раз
when Well, there were several theses
когда Ну там были несколько тезисов
that I directly remembered well. Cool
которые я прямо помнил хорошо Классно Не
No, now, look now, you’re
ну сейчас смотри сейчас у вас есть
just excited because I’m still,
просто волнение потому что я всё-таки
like, a person of more, let’s say, strong
как бы человек более скажем сильной
charisma, and you internally feel
харизмы так и вы внутренне ощущаете
this kind of dominance  over yourself,
такое вот как бы доминирование над собой
therefore, you may be a little tusheva and
поэтому вы может немножко тушева и
Forgotten, that is, if this often manifests itself in you,
Забыли то есть если у вас часто это
then you need to
проявляется да тогда уже нужно
turn to a psychotherapist. If only
обратиться к психотерапевт Если только
today, then it’s not scary. Well, yes, I understand,
сегодня то это не страшно Ну да Понятно
thank you, yes, well, then maybe you’ll remember what else
спасибо да ну то может вспомните что ещё
from this book can Take what you have
из этой книги может Возьмите что вы там
written out on the phone Look Thanks
выписали в телефоне Посмотрите Спасибо
for the permission Uh-huh, but you read this
за разрешение Угу а вы же читали эту
book, yes, this is the basis, it’s a
книгу да это же основа это ба
professional, it’s the same basis
профессионал это же база
Yes, it seems to me what other books you can
Да как мне кажется какие может ещё книги
recommend on psychology that are not related to
посоветуете по психологии не связанные с
the war with a military conflict with anything
войной с военным конфликтом ни с чем
just for yourself  It wouldn’t be
просто так для себя чтобы не жить было
easier to live so that your life would be easier Well, it’s
проще чтобы вам жить было проще Ну да
easier to understand the buzz Look, I would
проще понятней кайфо Смотри Я бы
advise You don’t need to read books here
посоветовал Тут вам не книги надо читать
You need to go through this one and it’s not your course,
Вам нужно пройти такую и не Ваш курс
just not not not my course not I don’t
только вот не не не мой курс не я вам не
give you my course Like you don’t tell me  you will be able to
впа свой курс Типа вы мне не сможете
transfer money You are in another country
перевести деньги Вы же в другой стране
Look uh The fact is that there is such a
Смотри э Дело в том что есть такая
practice called renunciation of the
практика называется отречение от
problem, so you uh accumulate,
проблемы вот у вас э накапливаются вот у
you have problems at work in the family there,
вас есть проблемы на работе в семье там
well, everyone has some kind of conflicts
ну вот у каждого есть какие-то конфликты
and they all accumulate accumulate
и всё они накапливаются накапливаются
are accumulating Yes, uh, You once
накапливаются Да ээ Вот вы когда-то
went on
выезжали на
vacation, of course, yes, now you are leaving You
отдых конечно да вот вы уезжаете Всё вы
don’t work You don’t have anything to do with
не работаете У вас ничего не связ с
work, you are liberated
работой вы раскрепощенной
Yes, you are constantly every day, something is wrong with you, you
Да вы постоянно каждый день что-то с вам
need to go on vacation so that you can get away from work
нужно выехать на отдых чтобы и от работы
and from your wife  relax For example, at least
И от жены отдохнуть Вот например хотя бы
for 2 days Take the boys and go out
на 2 дня Возьмите с пацанами выйдите
somewhere, for example, fishing Yes,
где-то там например на рыбалку Да на
just for 2 days at a barbecue, this is a complete
шашлыки просто вот на 2 дня это полное
detachment from problems and
отрешение от проблем да телефон
turns off the phone Yes, hanging out in short is easy,
отключает Да тусить короче вот просто
even if you are there talking about psychology
даже если вы там о психологии общаетесь
about the war, it’s not  war, the main thing is that it’s not about
о войне не войне вот главное чтоб не о
what you’re talking about, what you do every
том о чём вы чем вы занимаетесь каждый
day, and practice this thing at
день да и практикуйте такую вещь как
least once a month at least once a month
минимум раз в месяц хотя бы раз в месяц
Yes, if it doesn’t work out, then at least once a
Да если не получается да то хотя бы раз
quarter you need to practice If you
в квартал нужно практиковать Если у вас
don’t have this renunciation  from problems at
нету вот этого отречения от проблем хотя
least once a quarter this is already serious, that
бы раз в квартал это уже серьёзно то
is, if you don’t go out for 2 days at least
есть если вы не выезжаете на 2 дня хотя
once a quarter Yes, there are
бы раз в квартал Да есть могут
serious problems that can develop,
развиваться серьёзные проблемы
cycling professional deformation
зацикливание профессиональная деформация
change deformation Yes, I understand Class And if
смена деформация Да я понял Класс А если
there are books like these books
там книги какие-то по типу вот книги
Look dude, the book I'm telling you, you
смотри чувак книга Я тебе говорю ты
read 200 pages, you can't
прочитал 200 страниц ты не можешь
voice anything from it. You'll only voice what you
озвучить с него ничего Ты озву только то
read today. Tomorrow you won't be able to
что читал сегодня завтра ты не сможешь
voice everything that you said today.
озвучить то что ты озвучил сегодня всё
That's why most books are
Поэтому книги в большинство книг это
just literary garbage, well, it's not
просто мусор литературный ну не не
true,
правда
listen up.  wait for me, wait, you
секун слушай меня подожди те подожди ты
are saying that this is garbage, I don’t agree with this
говоришь то что это мусор я с этим не
because I drive before work,
согласен потому что я езжу перед работой
I just enjoy reading,
мне просто по кайфу читать
abstracting from everything, immersing myself
абстрагироваться от всего погрузиться
in my phone or in a book that Chita is the
вот в телефон либо в книгу которую Чита
same as tiktok you are immersed Yes, you
так же как tiktok ты погрузился Да ты
scrolled through but you didn’t  you remember what it’s about, look at a
пролистал но ты не помнишь о чём смотри
good book Yes, from these thousand
хорошая книга Да вот из этих тысячи
pages Yes, you can formulate everything
страниц Да можно сформулировать там всё
that is included there Yes, you can
что там вложено Да можно на две
write out theses on two pages Yes, the
странички тезисами выписать Да вот
rest goes there, uh, speech
остальное это идёт там ээ речевые
patterns Yes, illustrations like stories
обороты Да иллюстрации типа историями
when I once met my
когда я встретил там когда-то свою
employee there She  it was and that’s all This
сотрудницу Она была и всё Вот это это
is literary garbage, yes, especially
есть литературный Мусор да специально
because no one will buy a book of
потому что никто не купит книжечку на
three pages, really You’ll pay no, but
три страницы правда Ты заплатишь нет а
with thousands of pages it’s a good book on
на тысячи страниц это ж хорошая книга по
psychology, yes Therefore, look at all the good things,
психологии да Поэтому смотри всё хорошее
it’s clear and concise Yes, the rest goes
оно чёткое и краткое Да остальное идёт
somewhere else  chew the decoration everything
какое-то там разжёвывать украшение всё
so that it’s beautiful Yes, so that people
чтобы было красивенько Да чтобы люди
will buy it because printing is already a thing
купили потому что уже книгопечатание -
now I have
это сейчас
n’t learned the pages, it’s not true how I learned it
страниц не усвоил не неправда как усвоил
today Well, well, you didn’t learn it No, you didn’t
сегодня Ну как ну не усвоил ты Нет ты не
learn it no mastering Don’t call yours
усвоил нет усвоение Не называйте сво у
mastering - this is what you have left
усвоение - это то что у тебя осталось
after  in a month or two it will be
через месяц через два будет
gone You only remember what you
нет Ты помнишь только то что ты сегодня
read today Well, I’ve already memorized it all You
читал Ну я это запомнил уже всё Ты как
understand like a schoolboy That’s what he
школьник понимаешь Вот что он сегодня по
went through in class today, he’ll tell you what he
уроку проходил он тебе расскажет что
went through a month ago and that’s it Well, what’s the
проходил месяц назад и всё Ну какая
difference that’s it Okay Okay let’s go
разница вот так что О'кей Хорошо давай
I’ll run because I need to go on, I’ll be
побегу потому что нужно дальше уже буду
with my people at the training now, on the last
со своими на тренинге сечас по последний
question then where can I watch the broadcast?
вопрос тогда где могу эфир посмотреть не
It’s not private, we have a webinar type system,
он частно у нас типа вебинар система
we don’t broadcast on YouTube or on
есть мы не в YouTube транслируем и не в
Twitch Yes, well, it’s based on subscriptions like ours.
Twitch Да это ну по подпискам типа у нас
I’m saying that  ok Well then, ok, the
Я же говорю что окей Ну тогда ладно
last question since you all wanted to
последний вопрос раз Вы всё хотели меня
bring me into politics, the last question
вывести на политику последний вопрос
then this will be connected with when this will all
тогда с этим будет связаны когда это всё
end in your opinion and how much you
закончится по вашему мнению и как тебе
don’t
это не
like it are you ready to accept your answer
понравится ты готов принять ответ ваш
ready Yes, I accept yours ok yes it
готов Да я принимаю ваше окей да это
will end when  the last
закончится тогда когда последний
occupier on the territory of Ukraine will leave
оккупант на территории Украины покинет
it,
её
uh, with the Ukrainians, alive or dead
ээ с украино живым или мёртвым
Yeah, I got it.
Угу
Everything is fine then. Next
понял Всё хорошо тогда Следующий
question Now I’m asking you Why can’t you
вопрос Сейчас я вам задаю Почему вы не
admit the fact, let’s say that
можете признать тот факт допустим то что
people in Crimea conditionally didn’t want to live as
люди в Крыму условном не хотели жить в
part of
составе
Ukraine, I unpacked it, you opened it, you
Украины я распаковал тея ты открыл ты
opened it Well done open open yes
открыл это Молодец раскрой раскрой да
You see you are
Вот видите Вы
interrupting yes you are
перебивается да вы
interrupting Well I asked
перебивается Ну всё я задал отвечать
answer answer the question rub formulate the
отвечай на вопро потрите сформулируйте
question you can answer the question Look
вопрос можешь ответить на вопрос Смотри
when I studied we had such a Crimean
когда Я учился у нас была такая Крымская
program that people are from Crimea Well listen
программа что люди из Крыма Ну слушай
it’s not funny to be honest I  I’m silent No, well,
это не смешно если честно я молчу Не ну
if you’re changing Well, your reaction is not
если ты от меняешь Ну твоя реакция не
very like that. Formulate it, you see it, you’re
очень такая ен Сформулируй видишь это ты
embarrassed, look Wait, Look, I
стесняешься смотри Подожди Смотри Я с
wanted to talk to you normally, yes, I’m
тобой хотел пообщаться нормально да же я
fine, I’m waiting for the question, I’ll formulate a
нормально Я жду вопрос сформулирую
question. Why do you interrupt me
вопрос Ты почему перебиваешь меня
all the time, are you telling me
постоянно ты мне что-то говоришь
something -  then things that you are a cool psychologist and
какие-то вещи что ты крутой там психолог
psychotherapist And now you are sitting like a
психотерапевт А сейчас сидишь вот как
child, this is what I asked you
ребёнок вот это вот я задал вопрос
can answer Formulate the question You
можешь отвечать Сформулируй вопрос Ты
spoke a lot Formulate the question clearly I
много говорил Сформулируй чётко вопрос Я
asked the question clearly you can answer
задал чётко вопрос можешь ответить на
it Repeat the question why let’s say I
него Повтори вопрос почему допустим я в
should host your Maidan in Russia O  'Kay,
России должен принимать ваш Майдан О'кей
I accept it without any problems Well, what is
я его принимаю без проблем Ну что
the result of this Maidan, but you can’t
результат этого Майдана но вы не можете
accept the fact that some people didn’t
принять тот факт то что люди какие-то не
want to live there with the results of this
хотели жить там с результатами этого
Maidan,
Майдана
dude, your ears are very strong what kind of people
чувак тебе очень сильно уши какие люди
didn’t want to live with the results of the Maidan,
не хотели жить с результатами Майдана
where did you read that?  yes yes barbershop Where
где ты это вычитал да да барбершопе Где
Well, explain Russia led troops into Crimea in the
Ну объясни Россия вела войска в Крым в
Donetsk region of Lugansk now led
донецкую область луганскую теперь вела
Kherson and Zaporozhye we understood your
херсонскую и запорожскую мы поняли твою
pain you were ashamed to ask the question
боль тебе стыдно было это задать вопрос
but you overpowered You if you look at the
но ты пересилила Ты если посмотришь
chronology February 26 to 27, 2014
хронологию 26 на 27 февраля 2014 года
Russia occupied Crimea seized the
Россия оккупировала Крым захватила
parliament of Crimea state
парламент Крыма государственные
institutions, I don’t even interrupt
учреждения я даже не перебивай Ты
You interrupt you,
перебиваешь тебя
I’ll interrupt you, I’ll interrupt you,
пере пере я тебя перебью
I’m Ural sounds To be honest, I Know what you’re
я Урал звуки Если честно я Неу что ты
saying because I look at you, I’m
говоришь потому что я тебе смотри я тебе
telling you, it’s like you and I got burned,
говорю мы вроде с тобой подгорел
burned, turned off the sound Come on, I’m
подгорел убрал звук Давай давай я тебе
telling you that we’re good  they communicated
говорю то что мы с тобой хорошо общались
normally, as it seemed to me calmly
нормально как мне показалось спокойно
As soon as I started to somehow bring out
Как только я начал как-то выводить там
political topics there, this began, this is this, this is
политические темы началось вот это вот
acting, this is not acting, I’m
вот это вот актёрская это не актёрская я
like a psychotherapist, I disclosed I just no, I
как психотерапевт Я раскрыл Я просто нет
didn’t disclose, you disclosed te
не раскрыл ты раскры те
ra I’m asking this question to this
ра Я задаю этот вопро на это
question I  brought out barbershop barbershop I ask
вопро Я вывел барбершоп барбершоп задаю
this question every time I answer you. Why did you
этот вопрос каж я тебе отвечаю С чего ты
get the idea that people in Crimea don’t want to, well,
взял что люди в Крыму не хоте вот ну
wait, well, you’re interrupting me again, her,
подожди ну ты меня перебиваешь опять её
you’re interrupting me, you’re not a psychotherapist,
ты меня перебиваешь ты не психотерапевт
you’re not a psychotherapist, you don’t have
ты не психотерапевт это у тебя нет
such a thing. Let’s finish the deal, I’ll finish the deal for you
такого Давай договори договори я тебе
again  I’m telling you,
ещё раз говорю я
I calmly asked you a question, I’m
тери я тебе спокойно задал вопрос я тебе
answering you. You hear my answer, you
отвечаю Ты слышишь мой ответ ты меня
started interrupting me, you’re interrupting me, you
начал перебивать ты меня перебиваешь ты
said You yourself, I started answering and you
сказал Ты сам я начал отвечать и ты
started screaming, I’ll interrupt you and I started
начал кричать я тебя перебью и начал
screaming, I’ll interrupt you, so now
кричать я тебя перебью так вот а теперь
you’re saying that I’ll interrupt you  I’m interrupting You’re also a
говориш что я тебя перебиваю Ты ещё и
balab now listen to me So
балаб теперь послушай я те Так я тебе
I made the sound for you I made the sound for you and
скрутил звук Всё я тебе скрутил звук а
now you listen to me I’ll ask the question
теперь ты меня послушаешь я задам вопрос
differently I’m
по-другому я тебе
telling you what let me ask the question
рассказываю что дай я задам вопрос
differently You hear me I don’t don’t hear
по-другому Ты меня слышишь Не не слышу
Well, I understand  the question was that look,
Ну я понял вопрос был в том что смотри
you and I were talking normally, I
мы с тобой разговаривали нормально я у
asked you a question It was nothing
тебя спросил вопрос Это был ничего
like sarcasm, I’m really
такого не сарказм мне реально это
interested in this as a person who is
интересно как человек который
interested in history like why is this
интересуется историей типа почему так
happening I started for you
происходит я тебе начал
Answer this is not an answer really Yes I
Ответь это не ответ реально Да
agree yes I agree Look this is not
согласен да согласен Смотри это не
quite correctly, I told you not
совсем правильно я сказал тебе не
only in your ears,
только тебе в уши
but now look, I told you
ещ теперь смотри я тебе вот
and me too, say yes. If you
и мне тоже скажи да Если ты
said who didn’t want it, here’s Crimea Yes, you’re
сказал кто не захотел вот Крым Да ты
saying that Crimea didn’t want something with the
говоришь что Крым не захотел что-то с
Maidan, who told you this,
майданом кто тебе это
I can answer, you
сказал могу отвечать перебивать не
won’t interrupt  I allow you, well, you
будешь разрешаю тебе ну разрешать ты
will allow your wife, I allowed it once and you
будешь жене своей я разрешил раз а
’re nervous, you’re nervous, come on,
нервничаешь нервничаешь давай давай
come on, because dude, it’s
давай ну потому что чувак с такими как
really impossible to communicate with people like you. So come on,
ты общаться реально невозможно Так давай
answer Yes, look, this is based purely on
отвечай Да смотри это основано чисто на
your own social experience, social
своём таком социальном опыте социальном
research and
исследовании и
experience. That is, you’re just imagining  screw it up This is
опыте То есть ты просто себе накрути Это
your personal opinion You’re interrupting You
твоё личное мнение Ты перебиваешь Ты
think it’s cool or what Well, what does it mean
думаешь это круто или что Ну что значит
from your social experience, that is, This is
на своём социальном опыте то есть Это
your personal opinion was a social
твоё личное мнение был социальный
experiment I conducted an experiment
эксперимент я провёл эксперимент
social
социальные
research What kind of experiment how did you
исследования Что за эксперимент как ты
conduct it you like I asked questions to
его проводил ты как я задавал вопросы
people from Crimea and
людям из Крыма и
hall Well, you interrupt me constantly, I
зал Ну ты меня перебиваешь постоянно я
Because the methodology you came to
Потому что методологию ты приехал в
Sevastopol in the occupied Sevastopol Yes no Yes
Севастополь в оккупированы Да нет Да
Listen, you can talk, you promise, I
Слушай ты могу говорить обещаешь
allow, I don’t promise, Well, authorize again, I
разрешаю не обещаю Ну разрешать опять я
say, you definitely won’t give me permission 100%, I
говорю ты не мне точно будешь 100% я
will decide to authorize myself, I just
буду сам решать разрешать Мне просто
need you to let me  I didn’t interrupt and it
нужно чтобы ты меня не перебивал и всё
won’t work out, come on, Ukraine, so tell me
не получится давай Украин так Расскажи
about your experiment, you see, you’re talking
про свой эксперимент видишь ты говоришь
about the whole nation, you Ukrainians are all like that,
про всю нацию вы украинцы все там такие
you see, you’re throwing it at the nation. Explain
ты видишь ты на нацию бросаешь Объясни
how you conducted the experiment in
как ты проводил эксперимент в
Sevastopol.
Севастополе
Yes, come on,
Да давай
look at me, I’m talking. There
при Смотри у меня Я говорю В универе
was a non-Ukrainian girl at the university.  and the Crimean company,
была не украинская а Крымская компания
what kind of people from Crimea receive
что типа люди из Крыма поступают по
benefits, I asked a question, for
льготам я задавал вопрос у нас на весь
my entire flow, probably out of a thousand people there
мой поток наверное из тысячи человек
were about 200
было около 200
Crimeans, I asked them questions for myself,
крымчан я задавал им вопросы для себя
put some checkmarks Like
ставил какие-то галочки Типа так вот
this Vasily Vasilyevich, he is behind there Vasya
этот Василий Васильевич он за там Васи
Petro  he was against conducting social
Петро он против проводил социальные
research on VKontakte, writing to just
исследования ВКонтакте писал просто
random people, please They
рандомным людям пожалуста Анкетирование
wrote a survey and it turned out like this Well, of course not 98
писали и получилось так Ну конечно не 98
As we were told, not 98 significantly
Как нам говорили не 98 значительно
less much for several years I asked
меньше намного за несколько лет я просил
probably about Well, I don’t know 1 in my opinion
наверное около Ну не знаю 1 по-моему
was in the research this is a huge
была в исследования это огромное
social study you  you can’t
социальное исследование ты не можешь
say that it is small and the percentage turned out to be
сказать что оно маленькое и получился
that there were more people who wanted to
процент того что люди которые хотели
live with Russia, it’s just a
жить с Россией их было больше это просто
fact, I don’t want to somehow conflict with you now,
факт я не хочу сейчас с тобой как-то
it’s just a fact that
конфликтовать это просто факт который я
I saw and researched everything,
который я увидел и всё исследовал
that’s why I asked the methodology
Я же поэтому и спросил методологию
look, if you asked people who
смотри если ты спросил бы людей которые
came from Crimea to study in Kiev Yes,
из Крыма приехали учиться в Киев Да тот
you would have the same question and the answer would be
же самый вопрос у тебя был бы ответ не
different from those who came to study in
такой как те кто приехал учиться в
Moscow. That is, you agree that your
Москву То есть ты согласен что твоя
sample is not absolutely representative. Well,
выборка не репрезентативна абсолютно Ну
once again, look, wait, look, you  from
ещё раз Смотри ты Подожди Смотри ты из
Crimea, there are people who are from
Крыма взял вот есть люди которые из
Crimea. There are people who stayed in Crimea under
Крыма Есть кто остался в Крыму под
the occupation. There are people who
оккупации есть Кто под оккупации
moved to Rostov under the occupation. For example, they entered Moscow under
переехал в Ростов например в Москву по
some program. Yes, there are.
какой-то программе поступили Да вот есть
can’t answer something against
уже не может ответить что-то против
Moscow against Russia with this I agree,
Москвы против России с этим я согласен
everything is your methodology It’s just
всё методология твоего Просто она
falling apart No, I’ll say it again, the research
сыпется Нет ещё раз говорю исследование
that I conducted for several years It once again
которые я проводил несколько лет Оно ещё
you yourself confirmed that the person
раз ты сам подтвердил что человек
who came to Moscow and studies in
который приехал в Москву и учится в
Moscow He can’t answer  something
Москве Он не может ответить что-то
against Russia So I’m telling you later
против России Так я же тебе говорю потом
when it dawned on me This idea is that a
когда до меня дошла Вот Эта мысль что
person He’s already possibly something could be coming at him From the
человек Он уже возможно на него что-то
outside and maybe he Well, I don’t
может ити Извне а возможно он Ну я не
know on my own such Okay, let’s not take
знаю сам по себе такой О'кей не берём
this fact I  I’m telling you, I then started
этот факт я же тебе говорю я потом стал
writing to people in Crimea there,
писать именно в Крым туда людям
Sevastopol question Yes, look at the question uh
Севастополь вопрос Да смотри вопрос э
The thing is that I’m not a sociologist
Дело в том что я да Э не есть социологом
but I was kind of involved in some
но я был как бы задействован в некоторых
sociological companies Yes and I understand the
социологических компаниях Да и я понимаю
methodology yes uh there should be a survey
методологию да ээ должна быть при опросе
be
должна быть
confidentiality of the interviewer Yes, the
конфиденциальность интервьюера Да
person to whom you are writing on VKontakte he is
человек которому ты пишешь ВКонтакте он
already de-anonymized
уже деанонимизация
y well wait again I say they were lyu
й ну подожди ещё раз говорю были лю всё
anyway so we understood you you confirmed there
равно так мы поняли ты ты подтвердил
were people like you did there were people
были люди такие ты пове были люди
who answered against against yes yes you
которые отвечали против против да да ты
you confirmed once again the most important thing
ты подтвердил ещё раз самое главное
look here  uh Who were the interviews you
смотри вот э Кто были интервью ты
confirmed Yes that your interviewers
подтвердил Да что интервьюеры у тебя
were not anonymous Yes you
были не анонимные Да ты интервью
interviewed them those who moved there to
интервьюировать их тех кто переехал туда
study and who are dependent on the dean’s office And
учиться которые зависимы от деканата И
so on Yes, and wrote to people specifically on
так дальше Да и писал людям конкретно
VKontakte who personally page they have already
ВКонтакте которые лично страницу они уже
de-anonymized
деанонимизация
everything, well, well, look here  first, if
всё ну так ну так смотри вот первое если
we are talking about the scientific method, this is the
мы говорим про научный метод это
methodology of the methodology of the social survey. Yes, that the
методология методология соцопрос Да что
interviewer must give an honest answer, the
интервьюер должен дать честный ответ
most honest answer possible if his
максимально честный ответ если его
answer is invalid, uh, all this no longer
невалидный вот ээ ответ всё это уже не
makes sense, yes, that is, you can, this is all you
имеет смысла да То есть можно это всё
know in prison Yes, the prison authorities
что знаешь в тюрьме Да начальство тюрьмы
or they brought the researcher he  comes and
или привели исследователя он приходит и
publicly asks every sign of the teenager
публично у каждого знака подрост
whether the prison management treats them normally,
спрашивает Или нормально к ним относится
what do you think the
руководство тюрьмы как думаешь какой
survey will be like? Well, okay, why don’t you
будет опрос Ну хорошо А почему ты не
take the fact that people really
берёшь тот факт то что люди реально
wanted to live with Russia, yes, I
хотели жить с Россией е ри те я тебя
asked you where you referred me to your
спросил откуда ты мне сослался на своё
research  We just figured out
исследование Мы только что разобрались
that your research I don’t understand
что твоё исследование Поня нет
Once again Go Look, you yourself confirmed
Раз ещ раз Го Смотри ты сам подтвердил
that Verdi’s interview that this fact can
что интервью Верди что этот факт может
slightly increase what
чуть-чуть увеличить
people are counting on Ask any
люди Спроси у любого
sociologist if a person yes feels the
социолога если человек да чувствует
danger of answering Does it make sense to
опасность ответа Имеет ли смысл у него
ask him no everything so look  and if a
опрашивать нет всё так смотри а если
person already seems to enjoy living in
человек уже как бы ему кайфово жить в
Russia, why does he How do you know, look
России почему он Откуда ты знаешь смотри
in order to ask This is necessary to
для того чтобы спросить Это надо
ask anonymously whether it’s a thrill or not for
анонимно спросить кайфово или не кайфово
him to live in Russia if you approach Yes, and you
ему жить в России если ты подходишь Да и
say Ivan Ivanovich
говоришь Иван Иванович Скажите
Please tell me it’s a thrill to live in Russia or
пожалуйста Вам кайфово жить в России или
you  our government is not satisfied with what do
Вас не устраивает наша власть Как
you think a person
думаешь что человек
will answer in Russia if if he is,
ответит в России если если он будет ну
well, damn, I understand, the answer is that it will be necessary to
блин я понял ответит то что надо будет
answer, that’s all, and they answered you
ответить вот всё так и тебе отвечали то
absolutely what you need. Well, yes, well, why
что надо абсолютно Ну да Ну а почему ещ
again? Look, you just somehow understand
раз Смотри ты просто какой-то понимаешь
You  you yourself say that the person will not
Ты сам же говоришь что человек не будет
answer honestly and now you say no
отвечать честно и теперь говоришь нет
no because the research is different Let’s
нет потому что исследование разное Давай
evaluate Putin’s policies and it’s just
будем оценивать политику Путина и просто
fun for you to live Well, it’s good to live in Russia
вам кайфово жить Ну хорошо жить в России
different questions
разных вопро
with What Come on, so are you in your research
с Какое Давай так ты в своём исле какой
what is the question you asked in  In my
вот какой вопрос Ты задавал в своём
interview, I asked that you are for life
интервью я спрашивал то что вы за жизнь
in Russia or for life in Ukraine, the form is not
с России либо за жизнь Укра сформу не
Well, take exactly how it was
Вот возьми точно как оно было
formulated, I once again say the exact
сформулировано я ещё раз говорю точно
question Are you for life in Russia or for life
вопрос Вы за жизнь в России или за жизнь
in Ukraine are you for one question Yes, you
в Украине ты за один вопрос Да один
asked one question Well yes  and there you
вопрос задавал Ну да и там это галочку
just put a checkmark and everything is like a checkmark, like
просто поставить и всё как галочку как
you sent a checkmark on VKontakte Dude in
ты ВКонтакте галочку высылала Чувак в
Yandex you can create an account if you
Яндексе можно создавать анке
want anything It’s also like Sole In short,
хоче всё Оно ещё типа Соле Всё короче
dude is not funny at all, listen,
чувак вообще не смешно ну слушай
let’s finish it again Well, I’m already
давай ещё раз что ты закончить Ну я уже
finishing for you, look, come on
заканчиваю за тебя смотри ты Давай
undercut you interviewed students who
подрез ты опросил студентов которые
came to Moscow Do they want to live in
приехали в Москву Хотят ли они жить в
Russia and wrote to people who zat
России да писал людям которые зат
from handsome burnt burnt cool
от красавчик подгорел подгорел классно
we grew you up
мы тебя расли
about Rakovo it’s just beautiful beautiful you
проу Раково просто красиво красиво тебя
So they promoted you, you’ll throw money on my
Так раскрутили скинешь Бабки мне на
card, then we’ll
карту потом
send it to you In short, we won’t, we won’t throw it off Tell me the
за скинем тебе Короче не не скинем
address  in his country, he
Говори адрес в своей стране такой
says, of course, we’ll send it,
говорит конечно пришлём
in short, there are guys, we pass it on to them, they
короче есть ребята мы им передаём они
throw it off, really,
скидывает реально
oh, I’ll throw it off, dude, you’re just the
ой скину те не Чувак ты прямо
most
максимально
Mega I’m the king of all, I’m the king of
какой-то Мега Я король всех Я король
Ukrainian propaganda, the king of the TsPSO, in short,
украинской пропаганды король цпсо короче
in the end, you didn’t answer my main question
в итоге ты на главный вопрос мой не
I you I  ruined you on your
ответил Я тебя я тебя развалил по твоему
question You said look you said
вопросу Ты сказал смотри ты сказал
Why did I ask on the basis of what and all
Почему я спросил на основании чего и всё
you could say was that based on
что ты смог сказать что на основании
my research when we you
моего исследования когда мы ты его даже
didn’t even conduct it You even when we looked at
не проводил Ты даже когда мы посмотрели
our research Look I’m
сво иссле Смотри я
Techo I’m not someone with you  can
Техо я вами кто-то не может жить вас
all of you Ukrainians live no doy
всех украинцев нет дой
who is
кто
dark Donets Lugan here there are two
ть Донец луган здесь двоя
disputes
спор
you wanted you are typical Ukrainians you cannot
хотели вы типичные украинцы вы не можете
admit that it’s not you who can live with you
призна то что с вами жить
didn’t even turn off the sound
не вас даже не отключил звук
In short, can you hear me on horse Yes,
Короче ты слыш меня коне Да так вот
look how many people you interviewed in your
смотри сколько людей ты опросил в свом
research
исследовании
super I surveyed 1488 people from Crimea
супер Я опросил 1488 человек из Крыма
via
через
VKontakte right away I surveyed 1488 of them
ВКонтакт прально Я опросили 1488 из них
1400 said that Russia should
1400 сказали что Россия должна
fall apart I have been done I
развалиться меня сделаны есть у меня
have a study 1488 people surveyed
есть исследование 1488 человек опрошено
1400 it’s a thrill just a blast today I
1400 кайф просто кайф сегодня распаковал
just unpacked it And so msya mvsya msya class
просто А так мся мвся мся класс
put plus who got a kick out of today’s
поставьте плюс кто кайфанул сегодняшней
unpacking  just mega awesome like we from the
распаковки просто мега офигенно як мы из
TsGO like barber unpacked such a
цго типа барбера распаковали такой
reference
эталонного
Ukraine woke up in you because the edge of the
Украин проснулся в тебе пому что покрай
psychotherapist from
психотерапевт из
you is tro and will show everyone and everyone will see
теб тро и покажет всем и все увидят
because the priests are the king of the TsPSO Glory to
потому что попы король цпсо Слава
Ukraine we can do it and Russia will fall apart
украини мы переможе а росия развалиться
write like and deprive the comment
пишиться поставте лайк и лишить комент
so that the video is maximal
чтоб видео максимально
dry on my Telegram directly at once axis
просуши на мий Telegram прям зараз ось
VN and
ВН а
Popik is more and more respectful YouTube
Попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
taking us through the skarg ODS in your ban and even
заня нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и
more videos I don’t show people
дуже багато видео не показую людям
at all times I don’t show information about streams
вчасно не показуе информация про стримы
for this purpose for Mali operational
тому для того щоб ми Мали оперативный
link to write directly at once and Popik  there
звязок пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там
in telegra okrim video sche tezh tsikava and
в телегра окрим видео ще теж цикава и
korisna information and mi povinni z you trimati
корисна информация и ми повинни з вами
postiyny operational link
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine subscribe
YouTube Слава украини подпишись